(Sheldon:)These four walls
once housed an intellectual salon...
(Sheldon:)...where the mind received
nourishment as well as the stomach.
But through no one's fauIt, Penny...
(Sheldon:)...the quality of dinner conversation
in this apartment has declined.
(Sheldon:)And again, I'm looking at no one
in particular, Penny.
Fine. What would you Iike
to talk about, Sheldon?
Ugh. "What would you like to talk about,
Sheldon?"
(Howard:)Why do you hate us?
(Sheldon:)I've prepared a number of topics
that should appeal...
(Sheldon:)...to both the advanced
and novice conversationalists.
(Penny:)Okay, that time, you looked at me.
(Amy:)Who didn't? Your skin is like alabaster.
Do you even have pores?
Topic one:
"Faster-than-light particles at CERN:
(Sheldon:)Paradigm-shifting discovery...
(Sheldon:)...or another Swiss export
as full of holes as their cheese?"
(Sheldon:)And converse.
- Who wants to look at bridal magazines?
- Oh, me.
Through no one's fauIt, Sheldon,
we're leaving.
- Wait for moi.
- What? You're leaving?
(Amy:)Sheldon, sometimes you forget,
I'm a Lady.
(Amy:)And with that
comes an estrogen-fueled need...
...to page through glossy magazines
that make me hate my body.
(Sheldon:)- Well.
- New topic:
"Women: Delightfully mysterious
or bat-crap crazy?"
(Raj:)Totally.
What's wrong with cap sleeves?
(Raj:)If you have the right figure for it,
they're adorable.